{
  "totalQuestions": 10,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "The first three questions are relating to Animal Crossing Monopoly. How do you win?",
      "answers": ["Sell 20 materials", "Buy 7 pieces of furniture", "Highest Nook Mile total", "Collect 10 of each material"],
      "correctAnswer": "Highest Nook Mile total"
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "How many pieces of furniture are on the board at once in Animal Crossing Monopoly?",
      "answers": ["3", "1", "5", "4"],
      "correctAnswer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "Skill cards are acquired by buying furniture.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"],
      "correctAnswer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "The next four questions are relating to Monopoly Speed. Your turn ends after you roll?",
      "answers": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "How do you win?",
      "answers": ["Having the most property", "Completing the community chests", "Having the highest total of money", "Reaching $20,000"],
      "correctAnswer": "Having the highest total of money"
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "What can chance cards do? Select all that apply.",
      "answers": ["a and b", "a, c and d", "c and d", "All the above"],
      "sequence": ["a) Block a single opposing chance card from another player", "b) Gift free money to the player", "c) Force a player to put a selected property back onto the board", "d) Steal a property from a selected player"],
      "correctAnswer": "a, c and d"
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "What is given to you at the beginning of the game?",
      "answers": ["Chance Cards", "Community Chest Cards", "Properties", "Clocks"],
      "correctAnswer": "Community Chest Cards"
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "The next three questions are relating to Monopoly Plus. Who released Monopoly Plus?",
      "answers": ["Ubisoft", "Nintendo", "Blizzard", "EA"],
      "correctAnswer": "Ubisoft"
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "You may choose from ONLY preset rules.",
      "answers": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "What do you need in order to play?",
      "answers": ["A wife", "A licensed physician", "Paper", "Internet"],
      "correctAnswer": "Internet"
    }
  ]
}
